Guide to the Doris Duke papers on the Shangri La residence, 1932-2003 and undated RL.01434
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Records, 1935-2003 and undated
  - Invoice, roofing repairs at Shangri La. 1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Invoices, statements, and vouchers relating to the painting of the Playhouse ceiling. 1973–1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Invoices and vouchers relating to repair of the Qajar ceiling at Shangri La by Mark Forrest West and related DBO vouchers and invoices, and earlier repair work done to the Playhouse ceiling (1973). 1973, 1980–1982 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Estimate for S.D. Derelian for repair of Cuenca rug in the Entrance Hall at Shangri La. October 16, 1978, November 10, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Invoices for services rendered by Divingham Shipyard for repair to pools and pumps at Shangri La. Includes invoices for painting work performed at Shangri La. 1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Invoices for architectural services rendered by Louis Pursel and Associates. Includes an invoice for furnishing an inner spring mattress of Doris Duke’s at Duke Farms. 1979, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Invoices for repair work performed at Shangri La by Atsashi Okura. c. 1980s–1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Invoices for ceramic tiles from DBA China Clay for Damascus Hallway and invoice for rental of a large ceramic tile saw from Hawaiian Rent-All. 1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Estimate for roof repairs to the Roof of the Playroom at Shangri La to be performed by S&G Enterprises, Ltd. April 30, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Estimates for repairs to be made to textile items from Shangri La, to be done by Anthony P. Browne, Inc. May 1985–June 1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Invoice for purchase of table silverware for use at Shangri La. July 1987 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. July 1987 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. August 1987 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. September 1987 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. October 1987 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. November 1987 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. December 1987 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. January 1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. February 1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. March 1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. April 1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. May 1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. June 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. July 1988 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. August 1988 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. September 1988 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. October 1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. November 1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. December 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. January 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. February 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. March 1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. April 1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. April 1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. May 1989 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. June 1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Invoices and petty cash receipts for Shangri La (July 1989). Doris Duke’s grocery receipts (June 1989–July 1989). June 1989–July 1989 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Invoices from Sotheby’s for paintings, rugs, etc. June 1989–1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. August 1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. September 1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. October 1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. November 1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. December 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. January 1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. February 1990 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. March 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. April 1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Invoices and related materials concerning the purchase of brass lamps from P.M. Allah Buksh & Son in India for Shangri La. April 1990–October 1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. May 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. June 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. July 1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. August 1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. September 1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. October 1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. November 1990 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. December 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. January 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. January 1991–February 1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. January 1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. February 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Invoices, statements, and petty cash receipts relating to expenses at Shangri La. March 1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Invoice for purchase and shipment of Islamic Woa to Shangri La from Sotheby’s. December 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Certificates issued by Wyeth & King, architects, in relation to work done at the residence of Mr. and Mrs. JHR Cromwell at Honolulu, HI. 1936–1939 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Contracts for architects, supervisors, etc. 1936–1940 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Deed, construction Contract, and Power of Attorney Agreements relating to Shangri La. 1936–1947 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda regarding the Mahn v. Duke lawsuit. 1985–1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Ledgers and lists of furniture and fixtures. One list refers to items shipped to Paris from Duke Farms (1948). Another list pertains to Dodsworth purchases (1938–1939). Final list pertains to miscellaneous curtains, hangings, and sundries (1935). 1935, 1938–1939, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Location diaries of Doris Duke’s whereabouts. 1935–1963 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Lists of broken marble and tile, listed by cases, for Doris Duke Cromwell. 1937 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Progress report on alterations made at Shangri La. 1938, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Inventory for Shangri La. August 1939 (bound copy) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Reports of daily activities at Shangri La, Duke Farms, and Rough Point. Includes estimates for repair work to be performed on ceramics. Also includes appraisals of Doris Duke’s chandeliers and mirrors. 1966, 1971, 1979–1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Inventory cards (with photos) of contents of original Billiard Room at Shangri La. c. 1980s (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Reports of repairs needing to be performed on rugs and carpets. 1983, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Inventory of items at Shangri La. 1985 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Reports from Andy Butler for repair work performed at Shangri La. Includes photos. July 1986 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Reports from Nancy at Shangri La to Doris Duke regarding repairs and employees at Shangri La. July 1986–August 1986 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Weekly security report from Donald Nielson, Security Manager, Shangri La, to Bernard Lafferty. May 20–26, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Drawings of furniture and fixtures at Shangri La. n.d. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Maps of Kahana Valley, Koolauloa, Oahu, Hawaii. Maps describe master plan, topography, land conditions, existing land ownership, annual rainfall, and tax territories. 1953–1954, 1961–1963 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Catalogs from Parke-Bennet Galleries sent to Doris Duke. 1981–1984 (copies) (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Honolulu Monthly Statements of Receipts & Disbursements, 1966–1982 (1 of 4) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Honolulu Monthly Statements of Receipts & Disbursements, 1966–1982 (2 of 4) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Honolulu Monthly Statements of Receipts & Disbursements, 1966–1982 (3 of 4) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Honolulu Monthly Statements of Receipts & Disbursements, 1966–1982 (4 of 4) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Honolulu Monthly Statements of Receipts and Disbursements, 1983–February 1991 (1 of 4) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Honolulu Monthly Statements of Receipts and Disbursements, 1983–February 1991 (2 of 4) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Honolulu Monthly Statements of Receipts and Disbursements, 1983–February 1991 (3 of 4) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Honolulu Monthly Statements of Receipts and Disbursements, 1983–February 1991 (4 of 4) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Honolulu Vouchers, No. 33, June 1, 1982–January 31, 1984 (1 of 4) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Honolulu Vouchers, No. 33, June 1, 1982–January 31, 1984 (2 of 4) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Honolulu Vouchers, No. 33, June 1, 1982–January 31, 1984 (3 of 4) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Honolulu Vouchers, No. 33, June 1, 1982–January 31, 1984 (4 of 4) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 34, February 1, 1984–May 28, 1985 (1 of 4) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 34, February 1, 1984–May 28, 1985 (2 of 4) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 34, February 1, 1984–May 28, 1985 (3 of 4) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 34, February 1, 1984–May 28, 1985 (4 of 4) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 35, December 1986 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 35, November 1986 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 35, October 1986 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 35, September 1986 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 35, August 1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 35, July 1986 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 35, June 1986 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 35, June 1, 1985–December 31, 1986 (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 35, June 1, 1985–December 31, 1986 (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 36, January 1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 36, February 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 36, March 1987 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 36, April 1987 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 36, May 1987 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Honolulu Invoices, No. 36, June 1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Invoices and vouchers for miscellaneous rugs, bowls, statues, and other furniture at Shangri La. 1937–1938, 1953, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Invoice and vouchers for purchase and repair of tables. 1937, 1962, 1964, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Invoices for interior décor items and antique furniture by McMillen Inc. on behalf of Doris Duke. 1937–1938, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Invoices for services rendered by McGratty & Sons for services rendered with regard to installing marble at Shangri La. 1938–1939 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Invoices and vouchers for purchase of dressers, bookshelves, cabinets, and chests. 1938–1939, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Invoices for purchase of bowls and brushes for Shangri La. 1938, 1940, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Invoices and vouchers for the purchase and restoration of paintings. 1938–1939, 1962, 1975–1976 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Invoices for cleaning, restoration, and shipment of rugs at Shangri La. 1938, 1960, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Invoices and vouchers for purchase and installation of chandeliers, lamps, shades, and torcheres at Shangri La. 1939–1940, 1965–1966 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Invoices for purchase of dishes, trays, and urns. 1940, 1947, 1952–1953 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Invoices for candleholders at Shangri La. 1940, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Invoices for chairs, benches, and sofas at Shangri La. 1953, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Invoices and vouchers for repair and purchase of vanity cases as well as cigar and pencil boxes. 1953, 1959, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Invoices for reupholstery work performed by The Upholstery Shop on couches and mattresses. 1955 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Invoices for fabric and other materials for Shangri La. 1955–1957, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Invoices for services rendered by Louis Pursel & Associates, Architects and Engineers, at Shangri La. 1966–1967 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Invoices for the cleaning and restoration of a rug at Shangri La by Rugs, Inc., in Los Angeles, CA. 1987 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Invoices for cleaning of rugs and carpets at Shangri La. 1987, 1989–1990 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Invoices and memoranda from P.M. Allah Buksh & Son, India, for purchase of lamps and other items. 1990–1993 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Bills from Shangri La sent to the DBO. Includes supermarket, telephone, and other utility bills. 1991 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Real estate tax Assessment for Shangri La. 2000 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Invoice for transfer of “Honolulu Property” from Doris Duke to the United States (1938). Voucher for purchase of “home and lot at 1925 Judd Hillside in City of Honolulu (1941).” Memorandum regarding the purchase of the Wellcock property (1974). 1938, 1941, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Imports for Consumption form, State of Hawaii, for the import of various items to Shangri La by LADD Interiors on behalf of Doris Duke. 1975–1978 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Legal correspondence regarding the Corpuz, et al. v. State of Hawaii, et al. lawsuit involving Shangri La. 1997 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Inventory, Vouchers for items purchased at Shangri La. 1940–1943, 1969–1974 (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Inventory, Vouchers for items purchased at Shangri La. 1940–1943, 1969–1974 (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Inventory of items at Shangri La. Includes inventories of items at Duke Farms. 1967, 1973, 1975, 1978, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Honolulu, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Checklist for items going in and out of Shangri La. 1980, 1988–1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Photocopied inventory cards of decorative objects at Shangri La. Most copies include color photographs. 1985 (1 of 4) (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Photocopied inventory cards of decorative objects at Shangri La. Most copies include color photographs. 1985 (2 of 4) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Photocopied inventory cards of decorative objects at Shangri La. Most copies include color photographs. 1985 (3 of 4) (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Photocopied inventory cards of decorative objects at Shangri La. Most copies include color photographs. 1985 (4 of 4) (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Inventory of items at Shangri La. 1988–1989 (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Inventory of items at Shangri La. 1988–1989 (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Hawaii Residence Inventory - Entrance Hall, Entrance Courtyard, Inside Courtyard, Outside Courtyard, Ladies Powder Room, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Hawaii Residence Inventory - Turkish Room, Moroccan Room, Damascus Room, 1989 (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Hawaii Residence Inventory - Turkish Room, Moroccan Room, Damascus Room, 1989 (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Hawaii Residence Inventory - Mirhab Room, Dining Room, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Hawaii Residence Inventory - Living Room, 1990 (1 of 3) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Hawaii Residence Inventory - Living Room, 1990 (2 of 3) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Hawaii Residence Inventory - Living Room, 1990 (3 of 3) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Inventory of items at Shangri La. c. 1990–1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Photocopied inventory cards of items at Shangri La such as furnishings and decorative objects. Includes color photographs for each item as well. 1991 (1 of 3) (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Photocopied inventory cards of items at Shangri La such as furnishings and decorative objects. Includes color photographs for each item as well. 1991 (2 of 3) (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Photocopied inventory cards of items at Shangri La such as furnishings and decorative objects. Includes color photographs for each item as well. 1991 (3 of 3) (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Inventory of items at Shangri La. 1995 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Inventory of items at Shangri La, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Inventory of items at Shangri La. 1997 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Inventory of items at Shangri La. 1998 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Inventory of Shangri La (?), undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Inventory of Shangri La (?), undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Inventory, Shangri La. Includes bill numbers, undated (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Inventory, Shangri La. Includes bill numbers, undated (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Residence Photos, circa 1960s-1970s (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Residence Photos, circa 1960s-1970s (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Weekly security reports. 1993 (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Weekly security reports. 1993 (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Weekly security reports. 1994 (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Weekly security reports. 1994 (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Weekly security reports. 1995 (1 of 3) (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Weekly security reports. 1995 (2 of 3) (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Weekly security reports. 1995 (3 of 3) (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Weekly security reports. 1996 (1 of 3) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Weekly security reports. 1996 (2 of 3) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Weekly security reports. 1996 (3 of 3) (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Recipes from Shangri La, undated (1 of 5) (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Recipes from Shangri La, undated (2 of 5) (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Recipes from Shangri La, undated (3 of 5) (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Recipes from Shangri La, undated (4 of 5) (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Recipes from Shangri La, undated (5 of 5) (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Letter to Marion Wyeth regarding construction of Shangri La, 1936 Nov 28 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Items purchased from A. Rabenou. Includes inventories, correspondence and invoices, 1938-1941 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Various invoices for work performed at Shangri La. Includes list of records (vinyl) for new library, 1968-1970 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Appraissal for items stolen from the Playhouse at Shangri La, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence regarding Johnny Gomez v. Poepoe, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Copies of letters and memoranda from Shangri La. Includes copy of handwritten "My Meeting & Knowing Doris Duke Cromwell" by unknown author, 1975, 1987-1989 and undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, rugs from Honolulu, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - List of employees employed by Doris Duke, circa 1970s (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence and memoranda related to business activities at Shangri La, 1985-1991 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda to Miss Duke regarding work progress at Shangri La, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Memorandum to Doris Duke regarding "apple green clothing". Includes photographs, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence and memoranda related to pulley system at Shangri La, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence and memoranda and related materials concerning Shangri La's main entrance tile roof, 1990-1992 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence and related materials concerning electrical work at Shangri La, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Proposal (signed by Doris Duke) for plumbing work at Shangri La, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Warranty information for roofing system. Includes copies of invoices, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to pan tiles at Shangri La, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Work report for Shangri La, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence and other documents regarding insurance for three automobiles at Shangri La, 1988-1990 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Architectural Records, 1932-1940 and undated, approximately 180 items
  Includes blueprints, diazo prints (often with added pencil and crayon/colored pencil details), and pencil drawings detailing the design and to a lesser degree, later additions to Shangri La. A majority of the drawings date from 1937/1938 and are primarily pencil drawings of plans, elevations, sections, and detail drawings of both the interior and exterior of the home. Also included in the records are surveys, site plans, and schedules. The materials in folders C1D10F11 and C1D10F8 are of particular interest. Folder C1D10Fll contains 11 pencil sketches on tracing paper, presumably drawn by Wyeth & King. These are likely conceptual drawings of Shangri La, drawn in the early stages of the design process. Folder C1D10F8 contains record drawings, which document the completed project in great detail.
  Digital use copies exist for some of the architectural records and have been identified below. Digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access please contact Research Services prior to visiting the library.
  - Foundation & Basement Plan, Dr'wg No. 2A. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Oct 1. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F1)
    Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
  - Plan of Main Level, Dr'wg 3. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Apr 19. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F1)
  - Plan of Upper Level and Roof Plan, Dr'wg 4. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Apr 19. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F1)
  - Plan of Carriage Court & Drive, Dr'wg 5. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. undated. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F1)
  - North & South Elevations Section "A-A", Dr'wg 6. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Mar 6. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F1)
  - East & West Elevations Sections "B-B" and "C-C", Dr'wg 7. Marion Sims Wyeth, architect. 1937 Mar 11. Pencil drawing. (Oversize-folder C1D10F1)